Good morning, everybody. I want to start this morning by saying that, you know, you can set your norms. I never really knew that, but I know now I can set my norms. I have never, oh, I have never wanted to be dated. I've never wanted to be dated. I've never wanted to be dated. I want to be claimed.
And we claim and then we figure it out. The reason I don't like the concept of dating is because I am too much for you to be choosing between me and somebody else. And if you my nigga, you too much for me to be balancing between you and somebody else. So I've never wanted to be dated.
But we are taught that we got to date and we got to do all of this. And for some people, that's like their jazz. And I love that for y'all. I don't want to be dated. I want to be claimed.
So that being said, your girl has been claimed. I am off the market. I was on a 10-year hiatus. And at present, I am on a hiatus from my 10-year hiatus. So there's that.
Second, let me tell you something. When you see Lindsey Graham and Mitch McConnell dying, baby, baby.
The vibrant frequency is rising. Okay. They are out of here. Two ghouls have exited the building.
Wait, just to go back. Mumaji said, dating is bullshit. I'm telling you. I was like, listen, buddy. I'm not to be dated. I'm not to be dated. I'm to be claimed. I'm to be claimed.
Okay. So who's coming next? Lindsey Graham. And baby, like when they're like, it's right. So CERN closed. So for those who don't know what CERN is, I want you to look it up. I want you to look it up.
Do you already, babes? You good? Okay. So CERN closed. CERN was basically a machine that they built, that they built to fuck with time.
Okay. So Stranger Things is a true story. Eleven and the rest of those kids, they are MKUltra. If you don't know what MKUltra is, look that up.
I'm really trying to get y'all to understand that what you think is your reality is not. Because until you do that, you will not know what is needed of you.
Oh, really? Queen B Things? Is that right? Yeah. I'm going back and forth. So I just want y'all to rock with me. I'm going back and forth.
The reason I say I'm to be claimed and not to be dated is because I realize as like a grown ass woman who knows myself, I don't want bifurcations of your energy.
I'm not interested in that. I can't even figure out who the fuck you are if you fucking with me and then you got your energy split to fuck with somebody else.
I can't even, I don't even know who the fuck you really are. So, you know, but we, but we, we tell ourselves like we got to be the cool girl and da, da, da, da, da.
And again, for some people that is their jazz, but that's not my jazz.
You over here talking to this John and then you're talking to me and I know you're not talking to her the same way you're talking to me because I'm a different kind of nigga.
So it's like, you can't really get a feel for what somebody's, I want to see the full fucking you be.
I want to see the full you, but I never felt brave enough to say that.
It always felt like that's you doing too much. No, if that's doing too much, baby, call me TM, not trademark.
No. And you know, listen, if it don't work, it don't work. But is it my crush? No, it's not my crush.
My crush is married. No. Um, but same vibes, same vibes.
So, you know, it's, it's like, I'm just, I'm, I'm just trying to demonstrate for folks in my own, through, through my own experience.
Cause that's what I've been brought here on this realm to do, to, to basically demonstrate ways that we can live through my own hardships, et cetera.
And finding my way through them. And I'm really wanting to encourage y'all, be who the fuck you are.
Be who you are. Stop holding yourself back for people. Be who you are. Be who you are.
We are so, um, oh, my crush is my villain. He know that though. Be who you are.
Please. Because even being who you are outside of dating and shit, being who you are and your authenticity is revolutionary.
It is literally an act of resistance to be who you are in a world that is continually telling you how to be.
Speaking of you, QC is funny. Don't tell me what to fucking do.
I'm going to talk about what I want to talk about when I'm talking about it. And I will absolutely talk about CERN, but ask me, do not demand of me.
Ask me, do not demand of me. Can you please talk about CERN more? Thank you.
Ask me, don't demand of me. Be your full fucking self.
And whoever is for you will fuck with that until maybe they don't because sometimes frequencies change.
However, I will tell you that this is the first time I was ever my full fucking self.
And the nigga's like, I'm trying to sign up for this. This is confusing and fascinating.
You don't need to be how you are in corporate America. I'm not talking about corporate America.
Yes, QC is funny. I got you, baby.
Corporate America, go and get your fucking money for the time that money exists.
Millie said, what jungle are you in? I'm in my backyard.
Go and get your money while money exists so that you can exist.
Okay. However, Thomas Page, you are literally an embodiment of revolution as a trans person
because you are breaking the binary and the binary is a fucking lie.
The binary is a lie. All of this shit is a fucking lie that controls you.
Anything that is controlling you is a lie.
So, Jordi, you okay?
Trying to find somewhere to bury his true toy.
So, I say all that to say, you know, in this era of Aquarius and finding our true selves,
I have a song on my album called Let's Make Out that talks about there's romance and revolution.
There has to be romance and revolution because love is growth and growth is revolutionary in a world that destroys.
In a world built on destruction, love is growth.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
The reason it's growth is not necessarily because you make a baby.
It's growth because it's two energies coming together.
And we all know that energy coming together with other energy is expanding energy.
That's growth. That is growth.
This is the type of shit I'm going to be talking about on my new radio show on Tata Smiley's radio network, KBLA Talk 1580.
Every Friday, you can listen to me.
You know, we are in a world that literally is built on destruction.
It's constantly destruction, destruction, destruction, destruction.
So, love is revolutionary.
So, that also means love yourself for who you are.
But you got to learn who you are.
You got to learn who you are.
You got to learn what are the parts about you that you like?
What are the parts about you that you don't like that you can lean into?
How did those parts even form?
Get to the bottom of that.
Okay?
What is the parts about you that people don't like and understand?
Why don't they like them?
Understand why they don't like them.
You know why I started going to therapy in 2015?
Because everybody kept telling me I was mean.
That's why I started going to therapy in 2015.
And the nigga, my man, my man was like, you're not mean.
You just direct.
And people don't like that.
People don't want you to tell the truth.
People don't want you to keep it a buck.
People don't want you to talk straight up.
So, they're going to call you a meme because you're talking soon.
And you have to determine, okay, is what people are saying about me true?
Or is it just contextualized in the midst of a world that doesn't want that?
So, like, this brother right here, QC, is funny.
He told me what to do instead of asking me.
When you ask somebody, you are giving them space to choose.
And this whole life is based on choice.
This whole life.
Like, no matter what you believe in, no matter what God you believe in, this is free will.
You said, are we still together?
We just got together.
Oh, yeah, I have a new man.
I would never refer to an ex as my man.
Ever.
I would say my man at the time.
But I would never refer to an ex just casually as my man.
Never.
Ever, ever, ever, ever.
Them niggas out.
They out, Leona.
They out.
So, on this Sunday morning, some things I just wanted to impart to folks is really just being aware of the fact that, like, things are being manipulated around you.
So, let's talk about CERN.
CERN is a program that is, that was created to fuck with time.
To fuck with, well, basically it's to fuck with electrons.
And electrons determine time.
Okay?
And determine our understanding of time and our relationship to time.
Because all of this is built on electrons.
This whole fucking shit is made of electrons.
And so, you can change your course.
You can change your journey by changing how you are relating to your experience.
Because electrons, based on quantum physics, based on quantum physics, electrons change based on how you are, how you, your perception of them.
Thank you, Joe.
My baby, Joe.
I love me some Jonah Castro.
Okay, they plan to reopen in 2030.
So, that lets you know.
We need to get fucking focused.
First of all, it should be shut down in other ways.
Okay?
So, CERN, you should always consider where things are located also.
C-E-R-N, CERN, is located on the Switzerland-France border.
The Switzerland-France border.
Switzerland is the home of, look at Jordy in the woods.
Look at Jordy in the jungle.
Living his best dog life.
Switzerland is the home.
Can you hear me?
Tell me you can hear me.
Let me know if you can hear me.
Can you hear me?
I believe QC is funny that it's not that the quality of life will be better for us now that
CERN is shut down. What it means is that there is less of a disruption of our ability to fuck
this shit up. That is what I believe it to mean. Now, remember, they be lying about shit. So they
may not have shut it down. Let's keep it a buck. They be lying about shit. So Thomas Page, I'm gonna
break you out your mind and say there should not be a fucking census at all. There shouldn't be a
census at all because everybody should be treated equally. Jordi, too far, babes, too far. So
Switzerland is the home of the central bank. It is the home of the Freemasons. It is the home
of the International Monetary Fund, the IMF. They all exist in the same building in Switzerland.
The reason why Switzerland is considered neutral is because it's home base. You know, when we play tag
and base is neutral, that's why it's neutral. The Swiss army protects the money of the Vatican
because they are in cahoots. Thank you, Ryann Janelle. Right back at you, Booski.
So when we... Thank you, babes. So when we are looking at where we're at and where we're going,
we have to start internally. If they're fucking with your energy, then you need to protect your energy.
Some people can't have this conversation because they are still living in a
if I don't see it, I don't believe it mindset. And what's wild is it be Christians. And I'm like,
but you don't see Jesus, but you believe Jesus. You don't see Wi-Fi waves, but your phone work.
You don't see the cells in your body, but they living. They doing what they do. So that don't make no
goddamn sense. We know that some things we can't see are working. We know that. Your energy is one of
them. Like you don't see the waves coming into the radio, but the radio is playing different
stations. That is what energy is. Your body is emitting energy. It is also creating energy.
Can you say more? Only one car me seven. Like this morning, you know why I'm on 10? Cause I just did
some yoga. I just got my energy together. And I got a man who want to watch me do some motherfucking
yoga. You're only going to hear positives until he does something negative. Just so you know.
Do you have any thoughts about the young man who went missing? Of course I have thoughts about
Nolan. How could I not have thoughts? I don't have thoughts. I have feelings. I don't have thoughts
about Nolan. I have feelings, you know, and I'm going to talk about this on my radio show
on Friday. We talk about police violence as we should. However, the fact of the matter
is that these crackers out here committing violence every goddamn day. They are performing lynchings
and we should be just as mad and just as angry because the system protects them the same way
the system protects the police. Tamela Horsford went to a sleepover with eight other white
women and never came home. And you telling me that none of them knew what the fuck happened
to this lady? None of them had to be convicted. None of them were convicted. None of them went
to jail. They tried to do the same to Ahmaud Arbery. They tried. And I want you to know that
lynching does not simply have to be from a tree. It is a group murder. And when we sit here on the
internet and simply talk about it, I'm telling you that we are actually enabling it. This is why I
stopped talking about shit on the fucking internet. Did you know that? That's why I stopped talking
about shit on the internet because we sit up here and we talk about it and we then have a pressure
release. We have, it's a release valve. We sit here, we talk about it. We, you know, that's what
therapy is. Therapy is talking and releasing. And so we sit here and we release when the truth is we
should not, it's not real. It's not a real release because we're not actually creating justice.
The release should be in the direction of justice. And so when we sit here and we simply just talk
about it, yes, you are soothing your nervous system, but you're not soothing or you're not
correcting injustice. And that's why I stopped talking about shit on the fucking internet.
Because I feel like every time we sit here and talk and I give you an opportunity to release that
pressure, it is working in tandem with those who don't want you to have the pressure build up
that is required to muck, to fucking rise up. That's why you don't see me on here talking about
Nolan. That's why you don't see me on here talking about Jay-Z. That's why you don't see me on here
talking about fucking Lindsey Graham and all this shit no more. That's why. Because we have been
trained to think that if we're just talking about it with each other, that we're doing something.
When really what we should be doing is standing outside that motherfucking house and threatening
to burn it down. That's what we should be doing. And QC is funny. I'm not just protecting my energy.
I'm protecting y'all's energy. Try it for a week. Try it for a week. Let me know after a week.
Try it for a week of not commenting on anything that is actually of material change. I'm not saying
don't comment on the corny, funny shit, right? Like if you see a fucking duck and a kitten
playing in a pond, yes, you should comment because that is joy.
Lean into the joy. Absolutely. But I would like you to challenge yourself for a week to not comment
on any of the fuckery. Instead, I want you to think about it. Don't let it come out so quick.
I want you to think about it. I want you to metabolize it and consider it. And people will
lie to you and tell you, you shouldn't be taking this negative negativity in. It's not about taking
negativity in. It's about how you're processing it. Lean into the positive. Process the negative.
Lean into the positive. Process the negative. If you see some motherfucking kids dancing fabulous
choreo, comment, lean into the love, lean into the love, right? However, I'm challenging you to for a
week, just for a week, just see, because it might after the week, you like, hold up. After a week,
I want you to ask yourself, do you have more ideas about what to fucking do? Do you have more rage to
refine? When you are not giving your, your passion back to this fucking machine? When you're not
giving your passion back to this fucking machine? I want you to, I want you to ask yourself how you
feel shifted. I'm paying attention to you and I'm paying attention to them. Oh my God. Oh gosh,
bibs. Y'all, I got Amanda's on social media. Woman of the wolves, y'all. Woman of the wolves.
Thank you, Donnie Bindu. It's not a break from socials. It's a break from how you're interacting.
Use this fucking shit to empower you. They are using it to disempower you.
Let the information empower you. You shouldn't have to, listen, you shouldn't have to take a break
from information and turn and let me calm down. You shouldn't have to take a break from information
in order to learn how to process it. Okay. Information is a gift. So if in order for you
to feel at peace, you have to disengage from receiving information, then you have been colonized.
They got you. They had me. They had me. No, we have to change how we are processing.
So the social media of it all is seek. I'm not saying don't. Well, I don't seek the negative
on these platforms. Like we live in a time where there is an immense amount of negativity
all the time. What I'm saying is when that negativity comes across your platform, instead
of responding to it, think about it. When you respond to it, it is a pressure release and you
need the pressure because pressure makes diamonds and pressure busts pipes. And we need to brush,
we need to bust this pipe open. So every time we see something on this shit that pisses us
the fuck off, whether it is Nolan's murder, whether it is Trump saying some corny shit.
Okay. I am challenging you that whenever you see that, instead of adding a comment about how frustrated
or about how annoying and about how stupid they are, I'm challenging you to instead take a beat.
I'm challenging you to instead take a beat and consider it, bring it into your mainframe,
not as a negative, but as an action that needs to be addressed. That is where we are being manipulated
and we're being manipulated in many ways, but that is another way we are being manipulated.
Our energy to address is being released back into this app where they then make money off of it
that they use to build centers, that they use to surveil us, that they will then use to criminalize us
to make us slaves. So I am challenging you. I'm not challenging you. That's not even the,
that's not even the language. I am welcoming you into a new thought process and to try it for a week.
Just commit to it for a week. When you see stuff on this app that is telling you about the fuckery of
this world, instead of responding in the comments, think about it. Don't give it away so quick.
Think about it. Let it walk with you through the world. Again, this is a pressure release
and that pressure release is what's keeping us. Whenever you see people saying we're not mad enough,
that's why. That is what I have deduced to be the case. We're not mad enough because we're not
letting the pressure build up. This doesn't mean that you can't have joy in your life.
Look what I got. Look what I got in my life. That doesn't mean you can't have love in your life.
That doesn't mean you can't have romance. That doesn't mean you can't have happy times.
And again, I just want to bring this back. Set your standards. So that's what I want to leave you with.
Remember, you can check out my new radio show,
Project Artichoke. Man, I don't even know what that is. I got to look Project Artichoke up. Shit.
Nah, the therapist telling you to just log off. That's some fucking bullshit, bro.
Because it doesn't tell you... Because at the end of the day, you can't log out.
They don't want you to do that now. They don't want you to log out.
I don't want you to log out either. Shit. My skin looks amazing because I drink water
and because I'm not allowing a negative man in my life.
I am receiving... I'm being referred to as queen and empress by a fine-ass black man.
Look at the knees. Look at the knees. Look at the knees.
And a nigga can cook. And a nigga can cook.
You know who don't want to cook?
Monica. Monica. Monica.
You're not wrong.
So, I will be starting a new radio show.
I want to shout out Tavis Smiley.
Tavis has always been a supporter of me, but...
You know...
I appreciate that he sees my brilliance and is also like...
Do your thing, girl.
Do your thing.
And so that's what I'll be doing.
Every Friday.
On KBLA Talk 1580.
So you can get the app.
Download the app to listen.
You can also listen on YouTube, but...
When you download the app, you're showing support to his network.
And when you download it right now, you're also letting motherfuckers know,
Oh, I'm doing this to support Amanda.
I stopped doing Amanda Land in March, Earn a Prize,
because I didn't want to keep being a part of the noise on the internet.
I didn't want to keep doing geopolitics because at the end of the day, that's not where my passion lies.
There are people whose passion lies in geopolitics, you know, and who are really fucking good at it.
You know, Brianna Joy Gray and Sabby Sabs and Aiden Simmerdane.
Like, they really thrive.
That's their jazz.
And, you know, for me, it's like, it's something I can do.
However, I know that that's not where...
Like, it was just...
It was a part of my process to where I'm going and my purpose.
Does that make sense?
So, I want to be making music and talking...
Well, not just talking, but teaching energy work and combining my skill sets of comedy and music and knowledge in that way.
Because, from my studies as a scholar, what I understand is that our resistance efforts do not stick because we are not aligning them beyond our politics.
They have to be grounded in energy and power that is bigger than us.
And we're on a fucking battery.
So, until we understand our connectivity and our literal energy source that we're on, which is the earth, and how we are connected to that as energy sources, none of our resistance efforts will work.
And, for the record, when you see these indigenous folks that are having successful movements, they're still connected to the earth.
So, that's why when you're talking about Democrats, I'm like, fuck a Democrat and a Republican.
Are any of these motherfuckers hugging trees?
Like...
And you may think, Amanda, what are you talking about hugging trees?
What I'm saying is that we are on a battery.
The earth is power and we are powered by the earth.
So, anyone that is trying to suggest that they're going to help and serve our, and serve your community, if it does not include protecting your environment, it is bullshit.
And I mean that literally.
I don't mean that esoterically.
I mean that fucking literally.
Any politician that you see that is not connecting the protecting of the environment with their politics, and that themselves are not a part of the environment, it's not going to do nothing for you.
I swear to you, I'm right.
Only because I come from facts.
It's just what it is.
This is not some fucking made up woo-woo shit.
It is ancient, and it is new.
Because it's ancient, and then you have quantum hard physics that supports it.
Understand your chakras.
Your chakras, you know, and the thing about it is that in the United States, we hear words that are from other places, and then it makes us, like, confused.
So, we hear chakra, and we're like, well, I don't know what that, that sounds like a word from somewhere else.
And so, then we shut our brains off.
So, either learn the word, or come up with a word that makes it make sense for you.
Chakra is just, it's just a port.
Yes, emojis are cave art.
You have chakras that line up all through your body.
The energy flows through them.
It's an extension cord with ports.
Okay?
You got your sacral.
You got your root.
You got your solar plexus.
You got your heart.
You got your throat.
You got your pineal.
You got your crown.
Them data centers they're building, they're in your body already.
That's what your chakras are.
They're energy centers.
Yes, Sarah.
Morning, K-Monroe.
We in New York.
Y'all thinking I'm in the jungle.
I'm in New York.
You know what's so wild, Nan Whitbeck?
Nan Whitbeck said we were all warned about New Age in church and programmed to hear these words as evil.
And even the fact that they framed it as New Age is a lie.
How is it New Age if it's ancient?
That's some colonial shit.
The only reason it's new is because white folks was discovering it and trying to share it.
They're calling yoga new.
Right?
Like, picture that.
What's up, my nigga Jordi?
What's up?
So, anywho, I gotta go because I am shooting an episode of my children's show, Raw Raw Radical Readers, today with my home, them, House of Infinity, Logan, and we're gonna have a great time with the plants.
Oh, God.
What are you complaining about?
I'm not giving you enough attention.
So, I'm gonna post this live.
I think this live was really live.
So, happy Sunday.
Remember, what I am welcoming you to consider is this week, instead of responding to negative...
Instead of responding when you see politics that pisses you off, hold it, process it.
We need to build up the pressure that builds diamonds and bus pipes.
Say bye.
Bark.